Finding Aid for the Edward C. Weber Papers, 1949-2005
Edward C. Weber Papers
- Correspondence
  - Dunbar, G. S. (reference: Elisée Reclus) (Box 15)
  - Duplex Planet (Saratoga Springs, NY) (Box 15)
  - Duroselle-Melish, Caroline (Box 15)
  - Dutch Society for the Integration of Homosexuality COC (Box 15)
  - Dwyer, John F. (re: offer to sell records of Political Committee of CPUSA 1927) (Box 15)
  - Dwyer, Richard (reference: labor education sources for bibliography) (Box 15)
  - Dykeman, Therese (reference: Gates of Freedom by Voltairine de Cleyre) (Box 15)
  - Dykes, Brent (reference: Outweek) (Box 15)
  - Dymny, Jerzy (IWW) (Box 15)
  - Dyson, Lowell K. (reference: radical farm organizations in the U.S.) (Box 15)
  - EIDOS (Box 15)
  - ELF (Eritrea Liberation Front) Foreign Information Center (Box 15)
  - ETHIC (End the Horror of Infant Circumcision) (Box 15)
  - Early, Frances (reference: photo of Agnes Inglis for her book, War’s Heretics) (Box 15)
  - East African Literature Bureau (Box 15)
  - East Village Other (New York) (Box 15)
  - East-West Digest (England) (Box 15)
  - Eberle, Ray (reference: socialism; St. Louis) (Box 15)
  - Ebner, David (reference: Benjamin Tucker) (Box 15)
  - Ebner, Michael (reference: 1912 Passaic, NJ IWW strike) (Box 15)
  - Echols, Alice (reference: photographs of Jane Alpert and David Hughey) (Box 15)
  - Eckling, Robert C. (reference: IWW free speech fight, Spokane 1908-1909) (Box 15)
  - Eco Contemporaneo (Buenos Aires) (Box 15)
  - Edcentric Magazine (Eugene, OR) (Box 15)
  - Editions Minkoff (re: History of the 2nd International) (Box 15)
  - Edizioni Revista Marxista Europa (Italy) (Box 15)
  - Edmonson, Robert G. (reference: IWW; note: researcher rejected due to academic level) (Box 15)
  - Edwards, Rebecca (reference: Mary E. Lease) (Box 15)
  - Effeminist (Berkeley, CA) (previously Agape and Action) (Box 15)
  - Efficacy (Harlingen, TX) (previously Innovator) (Box 15)
  - Ego (Marseille, France) (Box 15)
  - Ehrbar, Hans G. (reference: Mehrwert) (Box 15)
  - Einstein Papers Project (reference: Clarté) (Box 15)
  - Elliker, Calvin (Box 15)
  - Embardo, Ellen E. (Alternative Press Collection) (re: questionnaire for Alternative Materials in Libraries) (Box 15)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee (Box 15)
  - Emery, Larry S. (Box 15)
  - Emory, R. K. (reference: general) (Box 15)
  - Emig, Günther (reference: Erich Mühsam) (Box 15)
  - Emma Goldman Papers Project (Box 15)
  - Empty Closet (Rochester, NY) (Box 15)
  - Emirch, Arthur C. (3 folders) (Box 15)
  - Engelhart, Margaret S. (re: Robert Hayden) (Box 16)
  - Engelhart, Stephen (re: Morrison Swift) (Box 16)
  - Engelman, Peter C. (reference: Victor Dave; Nettlau essay on Dave (Box 16)
  - Englander, Bob (Box 16)
  - Enlisted Times (San Francisco, CA) (Box 16)
  - Entz, Gary R. (reference: Josiah Warren; A.C. Cuddon; 19th century intentional communities) (Box 16)
  - Eötvös Klub (Karolyi, Hungary) (anarchist group) (Box 16)
  - Epica Task Force (Box 16)
  - Epstein, Dona J. (reference: 1903 Haymarket memorial meeting) (Box 16)
  - Epstein, William (reference: Benjamin Tucker) (Box 16)
  - Erickson Educational Foundation (Box 16)
  - Ericson, Edward E., Jr. (reference: SDS) (Box 16)
  - Eriksson, Jerker A. (reference: Aino Malmberg) (Box 16)
  - Esch, Marvin (Congressman) (re: Guerilla Warfare Advocates in the United States) (Box 16)
  - Escuela Moderna, La (Calgary, Alberta) (Box 16)
  - Esler, Anthony (Box 16)
  - Esprit (Toronto, Ontario) (Box 16)
  - Esse Più (Milano, Italy) (Box 16)
  - Essenes of Kosman (Montrose, CO) (Box 16)
  - L’Europe Réelle (Lausanne, Switzerland) (Box 16)
  - Evanier, David (reference: Rosenberg; Sobell; Walter Goldwater) (Box 16)
  - Everett, Martyn (reference: Rudolf Rocker; British anarchism) (Box 16)
  - Everson, Judith (reference: Janus; Der Pionier; Karl Heinzen) (Box 16)
  - Ewing, Michael (reference: IWW; Woodrow Wilson assassination plot) (Box 16)
  - Ex-Priests International (contains only empty envelope) (Box 16)
  - Exile Press (Cotati, CA) (Box 16)
  - Exit (South Africa) (Box 16)
  - Exit Magazine (New York) (Box 16)
  - Eynon, Bret (re: Contemporary History Project) (Box 16)
  - Eyre, David L. (reference: Mother Jones) (Box 16)
  - F.C.I. News (London) (Box 16)
  - F.C.N.L. Washington Newsletter (Box 16)
  - F.I.D.H. (Box 16)
  - FPS: Youth Liberation (Ann Arbor, MI) (Box 16)
  - Fact (New York) (Box 16)
  - Fact Sheet Newsletter (Thailand) (Box 16)
  - Facts on File (Box 16)
  - Fag Rag (Boston) (Box 16)
  - Faigin, Henry (Box 16)
  - Fair Play for Cuba Committee (Box 16)
  - Falk, William (re: Rage, Mayday, Writing on the Wall, Torch/La Torcha) (Box 16)
  - Falling Wall Press (Box 16)
  - Falzone, Mike A. (Box 16)
  - Fandata Publications ( Fandom Directory) (Box 16)
  - Far East Reporter (New York) (Box 16)
  - Farmer, Louis (Box 16)
  - FaTGirl Zine (San Francisco) (Box 16)
  - Faulkner, J. Kaye (reference: Ralph Chaplin) (Box 16)
  - Fed Up! (Washington DC) (Box 16)
  - Federación Libertaria Argentina (Box 16)
  - Federalist (Washington DC) (Box 16)
  - Fédération Anarchiste (reference: Voline) (Box 16)
  - Fédération Nationale des Travailleurs Déportés et Réfractaires (Brussels) (Box 16)
  - Federation of Southern Cooperatives (Box 16)
  - Feeney, Joan V. (reference: Black activism in America (Box 16)
  - Feingold, Eugene (Box 16)
  - Felicani, Aldino ( Controcorrente) (Box 16)
  - Fellman, Michael D. (reference: Josiah Warren) (Box 16)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 16)
  - Feminary, A (Chapel Hill, NC) (Box 16)
  - Feminist Press (Old Westbury, NY) (Box 16)
  - Feral Publications (Australia) (Box 16)
  - Ferguson, Moira (reference: Gertrude Nafe) (Box 16)
  - Fernandez-Gatell, Inc. (Box 16)
  - Feuille Anarchiste, La (Paris) (Box 16)
  - Feuerwerker, Albert (Box 16)
  - Feurer, Rosemary (reference: The Unionist) (Box 16)
  - Fey, Ingrid E. (reference: Movimiento de la Izquierda Revolucionaria) (Box 16)
  - Fieger, Geoffrey N. (Box 16)
  - Field, Edward (Box 16)
  - Fier, Roberta L. (reference: New Playwright’s Theatre) (Box 16)
  - Fiery Cross, The (United Klans of America ) (Tuscaloosa, AL) (Box 16)
  - Fiese (Box 16)
  - Fidre, Jeanette (Box 16)
  - Fifth Estate (Detroit, MI) (Box 16)
  - Fifth Freedom (Buffalo, NY) (Box 16)
  - Fighting Woman (New York, NY) (Box 16)
  - Finkelstein, Ed (reference: general) (Box 16)
  - Finn, J.F. (reference: general) (Box 16)
  - Fiore, Jeanette (Box 16)
  - Firing Line (Indianapolis, IN) (Box 17)
  - Firstlight Pictures (reference: Hoover Dam, Boulder Dam for PBS documentary) (Box 17)
  - Fishbaine, Ben (Sonoma County TV Turn-Off) (Box 17)
  - Fisher, David (reference: Home Colony) (Box 17)
  - Fisher, Patricia (re: By-laws of the Republic of New Africa) (Box 17)
  - Fisk University, Race and Poverty Research Department. (Box 17)
  - Flashlight (Palo Alto, CA) (Box 17)
  - Flicker, Mrs. Robert (Box 17)
  - Flint, Maruerite (Box 17)
  - Flood, Reneé Sansom (reference: Clara Bewick Coby; Leonard Wright Colby; Wounded Knee 1890) (Box 17)
  - Fluxus West (San Diego, CA) (Box 17)
  - Focus Midwest (St. Louis, MO) (Box 17)
  - Foley, Barbara (reference: John Reed Clubs) (Box 17)
  - Folk, Richard A. (reference: Socialist Party of Ohio, 1900-1925) (Box 17)
  - Folke, Mrs. Edith (reference: labor songs composed in Canada) (Box 17)
  - Follett, Richard J. (reference: One Institute Quarterly) (Box 17)
  - Folsom, Franklin (reference: Lucy Parsons photograph; unemployment in the U.S. (Box 17)
  - Foner, Jack (reference: Captain William Edward Pattison French; William Buwalda) (Box 17)
  - Foner, Philip S. (reference: various IWW and labor questions) (Box 17)
  - Forbes, Ella (reference: Malcolm X) (Box 17)
  - Ford, Mrs. Merrily (reference: Henry Vincent) (Box 17)
  - Forristal, Brian (reference: Sacco and Vanzetti) (Box 17)
  - Forum (Berlin) (Box 17)
  - Forum for a Just World (Box 17)
  - Forum for Contemporary History (Santa Barbara, CA) (Box 17)
  - Foss, Karen (reference: National Organization for Women; Women’s Equity Action League) (Box 17)
  - Fourth International (London) (Box 17)
  - Fourth International (Chicago) (Box 17)
  - Fouts, Kenneth B. (reference: Eugene V. Debs) (Box 17)
  - Fox, David (re: sent photocopy of Emma Goldman postcard) (Box 17)
  - Fox, John (reference: Reuben Papers, Whittaker Chambers) (Box 17)
  - Frager, Cheshire (re: donation of Jack Frager Papers) (Box 17)
  - Frager, Jack (re: donation of his papers) (Box 17)
  - Frager, Michelle (re: donation of Jack Frager Papers) (Box 17)
  - Fragments: A Quarterly Journal of Individual Opinion (Bellerose, NY) (Box 17)
  - Fraley, Jim (Box 17)
  - Fram, Joel (re: donation) (Box 17)
  - Franeta, Sonja (re: gay groups in Russia) (Box 17)
  - Frank, Adelaide Schulkind (re: Alexis Ferm; Covington Hall) (Box 17)
  - Fraser, James (reference: The Mass Strike by Rosa Luxemburg) (Box 17)
  - Frazier, Nancy R. (re: survey of underground press publications held by libraries) (Box 17)
  - Fredericks, Shirley F. (POUM; Federica Montseny (Box 17)
  - Free: Gay Liberation of Minnesota (Minneapolis, MN) (Box 17)
  - Free China Weekly (Taipei) (Box 17)
  - Free Door (aka: San Diego Door, Teaspoon Door, Good Morning Teaspoon) (Box 17)
  - Free Men ( Options) (Columbia, MD) (Box 17)
  - Free Palestine (Washington, DC) (Box 17)
  - Free School, The. (Albany, NY) (Box 17)
  - Free Soul Magazine (Hartland, VT) (Box 17)
  - Free Soul Magazine (Hartland, VT) (Box 17)
  - Free Southern Theater (Box 17)
  - Free Speech Movement (Berkeley, CA) (Box 17)
  - Free Star (Hyattsville, MD) (Box 17)
  - Free West Indian (Grenada) (Box 17)
  - Free Women’s Press (Berkeley, CA) (Box 17)
  - Freedman, Eleanor (reference: Modern School, Stelton) (Box 17)
  - Freedom Bookshop (London) (Box 17)
  - Freedom House (Box 17)
  - Freedom News (London) (Box 17)
  - Freedom Press (London) (Box 17)
  - Freedomways (New York) (Box 17)
  - Freethinker, The (London) (Box 17)
  - Freethinkers of America (Box 17)
  - Freethought Today (Annie Laurie Gaylor) (Madison, WI) (Box 17)
  - Freeworld Times (Minneapolis, MN) (Box 17)
  - Frei Arbeiter Stimme (New York) (Box 17)
  - Freie Presse (Wetzlar,Germany) (Box 17)
  - Frenette, Geraldine (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Frenkel, Susanna (reference: Two Harbors Socialist) (Box 17)
  - Frente Homosexual de Accion Revolutionaria (Mexico) (Box 17)
  - Frente Obrero (Uruguay) (Box 17)
  - Fricke, Ernest B. (reference: WPA, unemployed councils, Voice of the Workers) (Box 17)
  - Fricke, James P. (reference: Brotherhood of Telegraphers, Knights of Labor) (Box 17)
  - Friedburg, Gerald (reference: Socialism in America, 1901-1919) (Box 17)
  - Friedheim, Robert (reference: Seattle General Strike (Box 17)
  - Friedland, William H “Bill” (reference: IWW) (letters date from 1953-1999) (Box 17)
  - Friedlander, Robert A. (reference: Spanish Civil War) (Box 17)
  - Friedman, David (Box 17)
  - Friedman, Roger (re: offer of Newsstand) (Box 17)
  - Friends of Malatesta (Buffalo, NY) (Box 17)
  - Friends of the Filipino People (Washington DC) (Box 17)
  - Friends Suburban Project (Media, PA) (Box 17)
  - Frihetliga Arbetsgruppen (Sweden) (Box 17)
  - Frisancho, Roberto (Box 17)
  - Fritz, Alvin (Box 17)
  - Frizzell, Robert W. (reference: Dr. Herman Schröder) (Box 17)
  - Le Frondeur (France) (Box 17)
  - Fuendo, Jim and June (Box 18)
  - Fulton, George (Box 18)
  - Fuller, Thomas (re: offer of anarchist newspapers) (Box 18)
  - Fund for Public Information (Box 18)
  - Fundación Pablo Iglesaias (reference: Partido Socialista Obrero) (Box 18)
  - Fuori (Torino, Italy) (Box 18)
  - Furey, Lee (reference: Arturo Giovannitti) (Box 18)
  - Fusca, James A. (reference: Cuban Invasion of April 17, 1961) (Box 18)
  - G.A.G. (Grupo de Acción Gay) (Buenos Aires) (Box 18)
  - G. I. Press Service (Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam) (Box 18)
  - G. K. Hall & Co. Publishers (Box 18)
  - GLC Voice (Minneapolis) (Box 18)
  - G.P.U. News (Gay People’s Union) (Milwaukee) (Box 18)
  - Gaceta Informativa (Mexico) (Box 18)
  - Gai Pied (Paris) (Box 18)
  - Gallagher, Dorothy (reference: Carlo Tresca) (Box 18)
  - Gallagher, Margaret (reference: Il Proletario, Benito Mussolini) (Box 18)
  - Gallo, El (Denver, CO) (Box 18)
  - Gambone, Larry (re: Saint Che) (Box 18)
  - Gamson, William A. (re: donation of Brandeis student protest materials) (Box 18)
  - Ganley, Ann (Box 18)
  - Garber, Eric (reference: defense of homosexuality in the anarchist movement) (Box 18)
  - Garcia, Guillermo (Box 18)
  - Garcia Duran, J. (reference: Spanish Civil War materials) (Box 18)
  - Gareth Stevens, Inc. (reference: permission to reproduce covers of Spanish Civil War pamphlets) (Box 17)
  - Garlin, Martha (re: donation of Masses and Metropolitan) (Box 18)
  - Garlock, Jonathan (reference: Knights of Labor Journal) (Box 18)
  - Garriaud, Joëlle (reference: Hippolyte Havel) (Box 18)
  - Garrison, Lora D. (reference: Elizabeth Gurley Flynn) (Box 18)
  - Garver, John W. (re: donation of 1960s material) (Box 18)
  - Gasperini, Laurent (re: donation of Arcadie) (Box 18)
  - Gauche, La (Brussels) (Box 18)
  - Gawrych, G.W. (Box 18)
  - Gay (New York) (Box 18)
  - Gay Activists Alliance (San Francisco) (Box 18)
  - Gay and Lesbian Historical Society of Northern California (Box 18)
  - Gay and Lesbian Latinos Unidos (Los Angeles) (Box 18)
  - Gay Atheists League of America (Box 18)
  - Gay Community News (Boston) (Box 18)
  - Gay Hotsa (Bilbao, Spain) (Box 18)
  - Gay Information Group (London) (Box 18)
  - Gay Insurgent (Philadelphia) (Box 18)
  - Gay Journal (London) (Box 18)
  - Gay Left (London) (Box 18)
  - Gay Liberation Press (Sydney, Australia) (Box 18)
  - Gay Liberator (Detroit) (Box 18)
  - Gay News (London) (Box 18)
  - Gay News Germany (Box 18)
  - Gay Post (New York) (Box 18)
  - Gay Scotland (Edinburgh) (Box 18)
  - Gay Social Democrats (London) (Box 18)
  - Gay Studies Newsletter (Toronto) (Box 18)
  - Gay Sunshine Press (San Francisco) (Box 18)
  - Gay Switchboard (Berkeley, CA) (Box 18)
  - Gay West (Saskatoon, Saskatchewan) (Box 18)
  - Gaybeat (Cincinnati, OH) (Box 18)
  - Gaycon Press Newsletter (San Francisco) (Box 18)
  - Gayer, Dixon (re: White Students League) (Box 18)
  - Gelbert, Bruce-Michael (Box 18)
  - Gemorah, Solomon (reference: Lawrence Gronlund) (Box 18)
  - George, Elizabeth (reference: IWW) (Box 18)
  - Georgia Straight (Vancouver, BC) (Box 18)
  - Georgian, Richard (reference: Alexis Georgian) (Box 18)
  - Gerard, C. E. (reference: SDS, “America and the New Era”) (Box 18)
  - German Television (reference: photographs of American anarchists) (Box 18)
  - Germinal (Trieste, Italy) (Box 18)
  - Gerrits, Lyle W. (reference: audio recordings of IWW songs) (Box 18)
  - Gersten, Raoul (reference: Henry-Louis de la Grange) (Box 18)
  - Gessell, Robert W. (Box 18)
  - Gettleman, Marvin (Box 18)
  - Gettelman, Marvin (re: donation of Communist Party shop papers) (Box 18)
  - Ghosh, Ishita (reference: Nigeria) (Box 18)
  - Gierstl, Bernhard (reference: Augustin Souchy) (Box 18)
  - Giffin, Frederick C. (reference: Bill Haywood; Mary Marcy) (Box 18)
  - Gilbert, Dennis (reference: Sandinista Party) (Box 18)
  - Gildzen, Alex (Box 18)
  - Gillis, Sunny Labadie (re: great nephew of Jo Labadie) (Box 18)
  - Gillmor, Daniel S. (re: donation of Friday) (Box 18)
  - Gilman, Lois (reference: Hamtramck) (Box 18)
  - Ginger, Ann Fagan (Box 18)
  - Gingles, Carl E. (Box 18)
  - Ginsburg, Steve (re: his survey of rural gay men) (Box 18)
  - Ginzburg, Ralph (reference: Ezra Heywood) (Box 18)
  - Gittings, Barbara (re: Gay Bibliography) (Box 18)
  - Givens, Maureen (Box 18)
  - Glaberman, Martin (Box 19)
  - Glad Day Press (re: New Patriot) (Box 19)
  - Glaser, Martha (reference: Association Silk Workers) (Box 19)
  - Glasnost – American Edition (Box 19)
  - Glazer, Joe (re: Joe Hill album) (Box 19)
  - Glenn, Robert W. (reference: Haymarket case) (Box 19)
  - Glenn, Susan A. (reference: immigrant garment workers 1880s-1920) (Box 19)
  - GLOB (London) (Box 19)
  - Global Tapestry (Lancashire, England) (Box 19)
  - Goddard College (reference: anarchist movement in Russia; Russian anarchist works in English) (Box 19)
  - Gold, Edith (re: daughter of Abraham Zubrin, friend of Emma Goldman) (Box 19)
  - Golden Legend, Inc. (Box 19)
  - Goldenfeld, Gene (re: collecting of materials on Blue Cross/Blue Shield strike of 1988) (Box 19)
  - Goldenseal: The Magazine of West Virginia Traditional Life (re: photograph of Mother Jones) (Box 19)
  - Goldman, Hilliard (re: Bendler donation of Inglis letters, cycling through Europe, etc.) (Box 19)
  - Goldman, Jon (reference: general info) (Box 19)
  - Goldstein, Leonard (The Goldstein Group) (Box 19)
  - Goldwater, Walter (re: Reuben Papers, Spanish Revolution) (Box 19)
  - Golin, Steve (reference: photograph for his book, The Fragile Bridge) (Box 19)
  - Gómez Peláez, F. (reference: Spanish Civil War holdings in the Labadie) (Box 19)
  - Gonzaga University, Spokane, WA (reference: Jay Fox) (Box 19)
  - Good Times (San Francisco) (Box 19)
  - Goodhue, F. M. (re: purchase of Commonwealth College materials) (Box 19)
  - Goodman, Dena (reference: Henry Bool) (Box 19)
  - Goodway, David (reference: John Cowper Powys) (Box 19)
  - Goosens, Miles (reference: IWW 19114-1924) (Box 19)
  - Gordon, I. Linda (reference: Moses and Lillian Harman) (Box 19)
  - Gordon, Michael (reference: Irish –American radicalism in NYC 1879-1886) (Box 19)
  - Gorn, Elliott (reference: Mother Jones) (Box 19)
  - Gosling, Bill (Box 19)
  - Goss, Robert T. (reference: B. Traven) (Box 19)
  - Gosse, Van (reference: IWW, Paterson Silk Strike of 1913; Cuban revolution) (Box 19)
  - Gotthelf, Alan (reference: Catholic Worker, Ammon Hennacy) (Box 19)
  - [Gowen, Michigan] Daily News (Gowen, MI) (reference: Michigan Ku Klux Klan) (Box 19)
  - Graduate Institute of International Studies (reference: International Möbel-Arbeiter Union) (Box 19)
  - Graeber, Dr. I. – Trade Union Courier (reference: William L. Hutcheson; Saginaw) (Box 19)
  - Graffiti Magazine (New York) (Box 19)
  - Graham, David J. (reference: The New Testament Basis of Pacifism by G.H.C. MacGregor) (Box 19)
  - Granhaus, Odd-Stein (reference: Scandinavian-American radical movement 1860-1940) (no reply) (Box 19)
  - Granma (Cuba) (Box 19)
  - Grapes of Wrath (Charleston, SC) (Box 19)
  - Grass Eye (Manchester, England) (Box 19)
  - Grass Roots (Texas) (Box 19)
  - Grass Roots Forum (San Gabriel, CA) (Box 19)
  - Graswurzelrevolution (West Berlin, Germany) (Box 19)
  - Graves, Dan W. (Box 19)
  - Graves, Goddard (reference: The Weatherman Songbook) (Box 19)
  - Gray, Carole (re: developing Freethought collection) (Box 19)
  - Gray, Katherine (Box 19)
  - Gray, Richard (reference: genocide of indigenous people) (Box 19)
  - Graymont, Barbara (reference: Daniel De Leon; Herman Richter) (Box 19)
  - Great Speckled Bird (Atlanta, GA) (Box 19)
  - Greater Detroit UAW Unemployed Coordinating Committee (Box 19)
  - Greater Kansas City Missouri Labor Council (reference: Great Southwest Strike of 1886) (Box 19)
  - Greater New York Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to the Human Animal (Box 19)
  - Green Anarchist (Oxford, England) (Box 19)
  - Green, Charles S. (reference: general) (Box 19)
  - Green, Martin (reference: Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, Bill Haywood, Paterson Strike, IWW) (Box 19)
  - Green Mountain Dyke News (Vermont) (Box 19)
  - Green Mountain Quarterly (Editions) (Oshkosh, WI) (Box 19)
  - Green Revolution (School of Living) (Box 19)
  - Green, Robert S. (aka Shane Green) (re: Anarchist Black Dragon, Carl Harp) (Box 19)
  - Green, Whitney (reference: IWW film footage) (Box 19)
  - Greenberg, Gerald (reference: Work People’s College) (Box 19)
  - Greene, Christina (Kate Richards O’Hare) (Box 19)
  - Greene, Lorenzo J. (reference: negro history (Box 19)
  - Greene, Robert J. (re: donation of Workmen’s Circle material) (Box 19)
  - Greenham Commons Women’s Peace Encampment (re: donation of newsletter) (Box 19)
  - Greenleaf (New Hampshire) (Box 19)
  - Greensboro Civil Rights Fund (re: purchase of Greensboro Massacre collection) (Box 19)
  - Greenway, Judy (reference: women in the English Anarchist movement, Dora Marsden (Box 20)
  - Greenwood Reprint Corp. (Box 20)
  - Greer, Rosalyn D. (re: Ron Greer) (Box 20)
  - Gregg Press, Inc. (re: The Invisible Empire by Albion Winegar Tourgee) (Box 20)
  - Gregorich, Barbara (reference: women and girls playing baseball) (Box 20)
  - Gremios Democraticos (Buenos Aires, Argentina) (Box 20)
  - Grenada Newsletter, The (Grenada, West Indies) (Box 20)
  - Greib, Aimee J. (reference: National Negro Labor Council) (Box 20)
  - Grimes, Andy (re: donation of co-operative materials) (Box 20)
  - Grimes, Ted (Box 20)
  - El Grito (Berkeley, CA) (Box 20)
  - El Grito del Norte (Española, New Mexico) (Box 20)
  - Gross, Jesse (re: donation of labor materials and death of Agnes Inglis) (Box 20)
  - Grossman, Luanne (re: Agnes Inglis research paper) (Box 20)
  - Grossner, David (reference: Black community in Philadelphia, IWW, Ben Fletcher) (Box 20)
  - Group Research Report (Washington DC) (Box 20)
  - Groupe Libertaire Louise-Michel (Paris, France) (Box 20)
  - Groves, Jay Voelker (Box 20)
  - Grubbe, Dennis (Box 20)
  - Grupo Gay de Bahia (Brazil) (Box 20)
  - Guardian (New York) (Box 20)
  - Guardian Art Room Workers Association (Box 20)
  - Guenther, Karl W. (re: Agnes Inglis) (Box 20)
  - Guerena, J.L. (reference: general) (Box 20)
  - Guerin, Daniel (reference: Grigorii Maximoff) (Box 20)
  - Guerinot, Joe V. (Box 20)
  - Guindehi, Salah (Box 20)
  - Gunns, Albert F. (reference: Centralia massacre of 1919) (Box 20)
  - Gutman, Herbert G. (reference: John Francis Bray, Depression of 1873-78, labor movement) (Box 20)
  - Habari (Mansfield, OH) (Box 20)
  - Haber, Al (good Weber bio info) (Box 20)
  - Hachey, R. Lawrence (Box 20)
  - Hacker, Abbe (re: The Anarchist Influence on the I.W.W.) (Box 20)
  - Haddad, Carol (reference: Eugene Debs) (Box 20)
  - Haessler, Carl (Box 20)
  - Hager, Lore (reference: German-American anarchists in Chicago in the 1880s) (Box 20)
  - Haggin, Bernard (Box 20)
  - Haglund, Elizabeth (Box 20)
  - Hahn, Manfred (reference: pre-Marxist socialism, John Francis Bray) (Box 20)
  - Haight Ashbury Tribune (San Francisco, CA) (Box 20)
  - Haines, Bill (reference: underground military press movement) (Box 20)
  - Hale, Jeff A. (reference: White Panther Party, etc.) (Box 20)
  - Halker, Bucky (re: order for LP from Revolting Records) (Box 20)
  - Halik, Connie (Box 20)
  - Hall, Roger P. (reference: sources for anarchist books) (Box 20)
  - Hall, Tim (re: Communist Voice, Workers Advocate, Struggle) (Box 20)
  - Halsema, Jim (from ECW re: donation of Philippine collection) (Box 20)
  - Hamburger, Joseph (reference: John Francis Bray) (Box 20)
  - Hamilton, Charles H. (re: donation of Libertarian Analysis) (Box 20)
  - Hamilton, James (reference: Josephine Herbst) (Box 20)
  - Hannan, Dolores J. (Box 20)
  - Hannote, Dean (reference: article by Ted Rausch in gay magazine) (Box 20)
  - Hansen, Jodi (reference: of blacks in the labor movement. See paper in uncat. ms file) (Box 20)
  - Hapotoc (Amsterdam, Holland) (Box 20)
  - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc. (reference: IWW photographs) (Box 20)
  - Hard Times (Washington DC) (Box 20)
  - Harding, Susan (Spanish anarchism, offer to donate Peirats Volume 2) (Box 20)
  - Harger, Richard (re: Shockley’s Sterilization Plan) (Box 20)
  - Harlan, Robert Dale (personal letter from ECW) (Box 20)
  - Harllee, John T. (re: Southern Libertarian Messenger) (Box 20)
  - Harrington, Helma (re: Seven Seas Press acquisition) (Box 20)
  - Harris, Craig (re: donation of radical literature) (Box 20)
  - Harris, Mark (reference: Randolph Bourne) (Box 20)
  - Hart, Jeffrey ( Dartmouth Review, personal letter from ECW) (Box 20)
  - Hartnett, Edith (Box 20)